[{"question": "When you're working on a project in a team, how much of the work do you often find yourself doing?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 0, "answers": [{"answer": "Most of it.", "points": ["passionate"]}, {"answer": "About the same as everyone else.", "points": ["serious", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Only a little.", "points": ["shy", "anxious", "carefree"]}]}, {"question": "You've been invited to go skydiving! Are you interested?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 1, "answers": [{"answer": "Absolutely!", "points": ["reckless", "brash", "tough"]}, {"answer": "Need to think about it.", "points": ["logical"]}, {"answer": "Not in a million years.", "points": ["anxious"]}]}, {"question": "What's your go-to snack?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 2, "answers": [{"answer": "Something sweet.", "points": ["jolly"]}, {"answer": "Something savory.", "points": ["easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Something salty.", "points": ["carefree"]}, {"answer": "Something spicy.", "points": ["tough"]}]}, {"question": "There are two boxes: a big box and a small box. Which do you open?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 3, "answers": [{"answer": "Big box.", "points": ["goofy", "brash"]}, {"answer": "Small box.", "points": ["mischievous", "calm"]}]}, {"question": "Do you enjoy looking at yourself in the mirror?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 4, "answers": [{"answer": "Yes.", "points": ["dramatic", "jolly", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "No.", "points": ["anxious", "shy"]}]}, {"question": "You're in a talent show. What kind of act are you performing?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 5, "answers": [{"answer": "Singing a song.", "points": ["passionate", "carefree"]}, {"answer": "Dancing with others.", "points": ["brash", "energetic"]}, {"answer": "Telling jokes.", "points": ["goofy", "mischievous", "jolly"]}, {"answer": "Performing a skit.", "points": ["dramatic", "serious"]}]}, {"question": "How would you describe an ideal gift for you?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 6, "answers": [{"answer": "Something practical.", "points": ["serious", "logical"]}, {"answer": "Something heartfelt.", "points": ["kind", "jolly"]}, {"answer": "Something unusual.", "points": ["dramatic", "spacey"]}, {"answer": "Something humorous.", "points": ["goofy", "mischievous"]}]}, {"question": "You're in an RPG party. What role are you?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 7, "answers": [{"answer": "Warrior.", "points": ["tough", "reckless", "brash"]}, {"answer": "Mage.", "points": ["goofy", "logical"]}, {"answer": "Thief.", "points": ["mischievous", "shy"]}, {"answer": "Healer.", "points": ["gentle", "kind"]}]}, {"question": "You're about to buy something you really want, but the checkout line is absurdly long. What do you do?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 8, "answers": [{"answer": "Wait as long as it takes.", "points": ["carefree"]}, {"answer": "Try to find it at another store.", "points": ["energetic"]}, {"answer": "Give up and leave.", "points": ["spacey"]}]}, {"question": "You're lost in a forest! What's your first instinct on what to do next?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 9, "answers": [{"answer": "Yell out for help.", "points": ["anxious", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "Look around and try to get my bearings.", "points": ["logical", "calm"]}, {"answer": "Build a makeshift shelter.", "points": ["easygoing", "gentle"]}, {"answer": "Wait around for someone to find me.", "points": ["spacey", "tough", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "Your computer has a software update available. What do you do?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 10, "answers": [{"answer": "Restart right now! It might be an important security update!", "points": ["anxious", "passionate"]}, {"answer": "Do it tonight so it doesn't eat up any important time.", "points": ["logical", "spacey"]}, {"answer": "Put it off as long as possible. It's probably not a big deal.", "points": ["easygoing", "reckless"]}]}, {"question": "What's your favorite activity to do in your free time?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 11, "answers": [{"answer": "Something relaxing.", "points": ["calm", "gentle"]}, {"answer": "Something active.", "points": ["energetic", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "Something fun.", "points": ["jolly", "passionate"]}, {"answer": "Something productive.", "points": ["serious", "logical", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "Do you daydream a lot?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 12, "answers": [{"answer": "Yes.", "points": ["spacey", "anxious"]}, {"answer": "No.", "points": ["lonely", "serious"]}]}, {"question": "Do you prefer a lively night out on the town or a relaxed night at home?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 13, "answers": [{"answer": "Out on the town.", "points": ["energetic"]}, {"answer": "At home.", "points": ["calm", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "How do you make new friends?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 14, "answers": [{"answer": "Just be nice to people!", "points": ["kind", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "Find people who share my interests.", "points": ["logical", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Get to know people until I know I can trust them.", "points": ["anxious", "serious"]}, {"answer": "I don't...", "points": ["shy", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "You have to call ahead to make dinner reservations! What are you thinking?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 15, "answers": [{"answer": "I'm happy to call them!", "points": ["jolly", "serious"]}, {"answer": "I'll see if anybody else would rather do it before I do.", "points": ["shy", "calm"]}, {"answer": "...Are you sure they don't have a website?", "points": ["shy", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "You're going for a walk, or maybe a run. What's your ideal weather?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 16, "answers": [{"answer": "A bright and sunny day!", "points": ["jolly", "carefree"]}, {"answer": "Overcast is best. No sunburn for me.", "points": ["gentle"]}, {"answer": "A little rain never hurt anyone!", "points": ["spacey", "tough"]}]}, {"question": "Meal delivery, yes or no?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 17, "answers": [{"answer": "Absolutely! It's worth it for the convenience.", "points": ["carefree", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "Only if I'm in the middle of something.", "points": ["kind"]}, {"answer": "I'd rather just pick it up.", "points": ["serious", "energetic"]}]}, {"question": "Do you ever watch sports anime?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 18, "answers": [{"answer": "Yes!", "points": ["brash", "energetic"]}, {"answer": "No...", "points": ["shy"]}, {"answer": "I don't believe in anime.", "points": ["dramatic", "goofy"]}]}, {"question": "What's your ideal vacation destination?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 19, "answers": [{"answer": "A bustling city! I want to see all the sights!", "points": ["energetic", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "Natural wonders in remote corners of the world.", "points": ["calm", "tough"]}, {"answer": "Visiting friends, wherever they are!", "points": ["kind", "passionate"]}]}, {"question": "What's your dish washing strategy?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 20, "answers": [{"answer": "A thorough hand-wash as soon as I finish!", "points": ["energetic", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "Throw it in the dishwasher, run it when it's full.", "points": ["logical"]}, {"answer": "I forget about dishes and let them pile up.", "points": ["spacey", "mischievous", "carefree"]}]}, {"question": "One of your friends is moving across town. How are you helping?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 21, "answers": [{"answer": "I'm there at the crack of dawn doing whatever I can!", "points": ["energetic", "kind"]}, {"answer": "I'm in no rush, but I'll be there to lend a hand.", "points": ["gentle", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "I'll show up... if there's pizza.", "points": ["mischievous", "goofy"]}, {"answer": "I probably won't be much help anyways...", "points": ["anxious", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "It's board game night! What are you bringing?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 22, "answers": [{"answer": "A crowd-pleasing party game!", "points": ["jolly", "kind", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Something more complicated, but I think we can handle it.", "points": ["gentle", "logical"]}, {"answer": "I know just the game! I own all four expansions and the Deluxe Edition and...", "points": ["passionate"]}, {"answer": "I trust everyone else to bring games.", "points": ["carefree"]}]}, {"question": "You're calling customer support about a package you never received. How do you feel about it?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 23, "answers": [{"answer": "I'm sure they'll get the package to me eventually. No sweat.", "points": ["calm"]}, {"answer": "If I don't make a big deal out of it, that package will NEVER arrive.", "points": ["brash"]}, {"answer": "...Maybe I can get the package AND a refund...?", "points": ["mischievous"]}, {"answer": "Why do I have to call them?!", "points": ["shy"]}]}, {"question": "At a fancy restaurant, which type of waiter would you be?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 24, "answers": [{"answer": "The one who does silly tricks for customers.", "points": ["goofy"]}, {"answer": "The best-dressed one.", "points": ["brash", "serious"]}, {"answer": "The one who carries three tables' worth of food in one arm.", "points": ["tough"]}, {"answer": "The one who always works in the back section, where it's quieter.", "points": ["spacey", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "What type of video games do you prefer?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 25, "answers": [{"answer": "Concise, well-crafted adventures.", "points": ["calm", "jolly"]}, {"answer": "Giant worlds to explore and immerse myself in.", "points": ["easygoing", "spacey"]}, {"answer": "Multiplayer games I can sink hundreds of hours into.", "points": ["passionate", "serious"]}]}, {"question": "You just found out one of your socks has a hole in it! What now?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 26, "answers": [{"answer": "I've got some fabric somewhere; I'll patch it right up.", "points": ["logical", "passionate"]}, {"answer": "Toss it; I've got plenty of socks.", "points": ["tough", "brash"]}, {"answer": "I'll just keep wearing it; who cares?", "points": ["goofy", "reckless"]}]}, {"question": "How many empty dishes are on your desk right now?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 27, "answers": [{"answer": "Zero.", "points": ["serious"]}, {"answer": "Just one.", "points": ["serious"]}, {"answer": "A couple.", "points": ["calm", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Oh... so many.", "points": ["mischievous", "carefree", "spacey"]}]}, {"question": "How good would you be at taking care of a plant?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 28, "answers": [{"answer": "I'd attend to its every need. I am the plant's humble servant.", "points": ["anxious", "passionate"]}, {"answer": "I'd keep it alive, water it most days.", "points": ["calm", "gentle"]}, {"answer": "It would be dead within a week.", "points": ["reckless", "spacey"]}]}, {"question": "You've got a job interview tomorrow morning! How do you prepare?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 29, "answers": [{"answer": "Practice for hours. Memorize answers and details.", "points": ["anxious"]}, {"answer": "Just a quick debrief before bed to make sure I'm ready.", "points": ["tough", "calm"]}, {"answer": "If I got to the interview, I'll be fine. Just show up and do my best.", "points": ["carefree", "reckless"]}]}, {"question": "Have you ever eaten peanut butter straight out of the jar with a spoon?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 30, "answers": [{"answer": "Yes. Regularly. And you should too.", "points": ["mischievous"]}, {"answer": "Only if I'm REALLY hungry and there's nothing else to eat.", "points": ["brash"]}, {"answer": "Maybe once? Not something I'd do again.", "points": ["logical"]}, {"answer": "What? No, that's gross!", "points": ["serious", "dramatic"]}]}, {"question": "What does your typical breakfast look like?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 31, "answers": [{"answer": "Something quick, like a granola bar.", "points": ["easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Something hearty, like eggs and bacon.", "points": ["tough"]}, {"answer": "Who needs breakfast? I've got places to be!", "points": ["energetic", "brash", "carefree"]}, {"answer": "If I wake up and eat at 1 PM, does that count as breakfast?", "points": ["spacey", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "How would you describe the moon?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 32, "answers": [{"answer": "A natural satellite that orbits the Earth.", "points": ["logical"]}, {"answer": "A beauteous wonder of the night sky.", "points": ["dramatic", "spacey"]}, {"answer": "I'm not convinced it's not cheese.", "points": ["goofy"]}, {"answer": "Ball.", "points": ["carefree"]}]}]